(They were startled and frightened,
thinking they saw a ghost.)
(He said to them, "Why are you troubled,
and why do doubts rise in your minds?")
(Look at my hands and my feet. It is I myself! )
(Touch me and see; a ghost does not have
flesh and bones, as you see I have.)
(Luke 24:37-39)
It's still dawn. What is it?
Somebody died.
Who?
You know Cho, the ginseng grower?
Yeah.
His wife died.
It's pouring out there...
Hey, where are you off to?
Somebody died.
Who?
Wife of the ginseng farmer.
That's all I know.
But she's so young.
You said it.
- Don't go without eating.
- I gotta hurry.
Just a bite!
Hurrying won't bring back the dead.
But I need to go now.
Eat, will you?
Come on.
What happened?
Not sure. I think someone killed her.
What kind of fucker kills people?
Damned son of a bitch.
Someone died?
Eat up, dear.
Who died?
Bye, dad.
What took so long?!
Gimme a raincoat.
Hurry up!
We've got two corpses here.
Where's the Captain?
He went to Seoul, remember?
Right.
Come on!
I'm coming.
Look at me, Heung-guk!
Let go of me!
I'm his uncle!
Jong-gu!
Heung-guk, how could you do this?
Sergeant.
Did it with this, I guess.
Stabbed him, like, 20 times?
Holy shit.
What's that?
Looks like the body was moved here
after the murder.
What a mess.
That's Cho- the husband?
Looks that way.
I'll be damned.
And the kid?
We took him to a relative.
Why'd he do it?
I don't smell booze on him,
but he's not talking.
Could be high on something.
How else could he end up like that?
What the hell happened?
How's it going, Sergeant?
I'm his uncle! Let go of me!
Rotten bastard.
Couldn't he use GPS?
Why do I have to take him?
Ain't that it?
Get the wire cutters.
Pull it back.
What's that stink?
So. Cho was killed here.
What the fuck is all this?
So he invited Cho over, killed him,
put the body in a sack, dragged it to
his house, and then killed his wife?
Crime of passion.
Make sure you photograph everything.
Here, there, that stuff over there.
Jong-gu!
Get over here!
Sergeant, come over here.
Shit!
Oh god...
That cocksucker.
What kind of twisted freak is he?
Is that scary, or what?
Scary, my ass.
Anyway, the whole town's talking about it.
Who told you that story?
Byeong-gyu.
That goddamned bastard...
Now he's spreading those
stories to you, too?
Well, from what I hear,
there's definitely something
off with that guy.
Like what?
The corner store owner went crazy,
The guy at the mill dropped dead,
and then Heung-gu turns up
dead two days ago.
So?
All this happened after that
Japanese man arrived.
Quit talking out of your ass,
you ignorant dope.
Who're you calling ignorant?
Look, the test results on Heung-guk
came back today.
Apparently, he ate some fucked-up mushrooms.
What?
You know. The ones with the drugs
that make you go crazy.
His blood was full of that shit.
And there were tons
of dried mushrooms at his place.
You really believe that?
It's what the results said!
Didn't you ever try those
mushrooms as a kid?
Hell no.
All I know is,
mushrooms don't do that to you.
You saw that poor guy.
Mushrooms would never make you that way.
But I'm right about the Japanese guy.
If everyone's talking about him,
there's likely a good reason.
What the hell?
Power's gone out again.
Fuck.
I keep telling the Captain
to get that damn wiring fixed.
Never listens!
What the fuck!
- What's wrong?
- What the Christ was that?
- That thing outside.
- What's outside?
- Outside, that... fuck!
- What's your problem?
What is it, man?
You check it out.
- Me?
- Yes, you! Dammit.
You want me to go out?
I'm telling you, asshole,
to get your ass out there!
For crying out loud...
Okay, I'll go.
Come on, hurry!
Shit.
Who the fuck are you? What the hell?
Stop, goddamn it!
Stop it, you dirty slut! You whore!
Eat this, too.
Amn, you're heavy.
I'm getting too old for this.
Don't be ridiculous.
Old ladies tell me men can
still get it up after 70.
Then buy me some herbal supplements.
I keep having fucked-up nightmares.
What're you doing in there?
Oh hell. Shit!
Nothing! Get away from the car.
- Don't open it!
- What are you doing?
For crying out loud!
Dad!
Dad?
Look.
How do I look?
Pretty.
Freakishly pretty.
How long were you watching?
How much did you see?
Don't worry, I won't tell.
So you saw everything.
No big deal. It's not the first time.
What?
Here.
It's okay. Have a sip.
Hurry up!
Son of a bitch!
What took you so long? Ignoring my calls?
My mother-in-law got sick.
Now you're using your
mother-in-law as an excuse?
You were taking a nap, I can tell!
No, I wasn't. I swear.
Get to work.
Excuse me, ma'am?
What the hell?
What are you doing? Stop her.
Yes, sir.
Come with me, ma'am.
Get off me!
Sergeant, get her out of here.
Back off, people.
What's wrong with her?
Please, calm down.
That idiot...
Calm down, ma'am.
Jong-gu.
Get cleaned up, man.
Hey, don't beat yourself up.
It's not your fault...
...that you're a little girly-man
with balls the size of peas.
Oh jeez.
Hello!
- Hey.
- Hi, Hyo-jin.
Hello, Captain.
- How are you?
- Good.
- You've got clean clothes for Daddy?
- Yeah.
Mom got you clean boxers and an undershirt.
Thanks, darling.
Take a shower.
I will. Go home.
You didn't even eat, did you?
All right, get out of here.
Can't you see Daddy's working?
See you.
Goodbye, officers.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- Take care, sweetie.
- Oh, my.
That scatterbrain.
Seong-bok?
Yeah.
It just hit me.
What?
That woman...
What woman?
The one whose house burned down...
I knew I'd seen her before.
It's that naked woman from last night.
What?
The woman who was standing here last night.
Crazy fools.
They didn't burn to death.
They were stabbed.
All three of them?
Yeah.
Freaked the hell out of me, too.
Prime suspect is the missus
who hung herself.
What the heck happened?
Beats me.
Over here.
In here.
What?
Give us a hand.
A little more.
Found it.
Idiot! Don't touch it with your bare hands!
What the...?
Are you a moron?
That's evidence.
He should've wrapped it in cloth
or something, right?
Gokseong Police Station.
So, she killed everyone?
That's what they said.
I'll be damned.
So, that's what happened.
Why did you call me?
Things are crazy at work.
Because of this case.
Remember what I told you before?
What?
How the Jap raped a woman?
What about it?
You filthy slut.
That woman.
It was her.
What the hell are you talking about?
That woman he raped-
it's the same woman whose house burned down.
She went crazy after that,
and used to run around naked at night.
My wife saw her at the public bathhouse.
She was totally covered in rashes and boils,
mumbling gibberish the whole time.
Are you out of your mind?
Byeong-gyu's got to stop this.
Talking crap to his dimwitted buddies.
You worthless bastard. It was your theory.
I was just messing with you.
Who in their right mind
would believe crap like that?
No, I think you're right.
It can't be the mushrooms.
That doesn't make sense.
Gimme a break.
What are you looking at?
Get outta here!
What?
Ignore her. She's been
doing that all morning.
What a nutjob.
So, how about you check
with the local dermatologist.
See if there's any medical records
on Heung-guk or that woman.
Stop it, you tramp!
I can't believe this.
It's important, you idiot!
The rash is the link here.
Come on, hurry.
Stop it! You could hurt somebody!
Community Health Center
Oh, my.
You're really getting on my nerves!
Where do you live?
Are you from this village?
Hey.
Don't come near me!
Dammit!
The lady killed them all.
What?
In there. In that room.
What are you talking about?
The old woman got
a shaman to do some ritual,
but the lady refused.
That's why they all got killed.
Are you a family member?
No, I'm not.
Then who are you?
Come with me.
Hey!
What the...?
You can't go in there.
It's all right.
Hey...
Come on.
She killed them here.
The old woman got it the worst of it.
Her head was smashed open like a watermelon.
You saw with your own eyes?
Of course I did.
How?
The old woman tells me
the Jap is a ghost.
He was gonna suck her blood dry.
The Jap?
Yeah.
The Jap with the limp.
Oh, him!
You've seen him?
Yeah.
How many times?
Once or twice.
Be careful.
Why?
The old woman says,
if you keep seeing him around,
it's because he's stalking you.
To suck your blood dry.
Wait here for a second.
Okay.
Get your ass over here.
What?
Get over here now!
But I just found the dermatologist.
I found a witness.
So, get over here as fast as you can.
What the...?
Where'd she go?
What terrible sin did you commit,
to be yelling like that?
Are you feeling sick?
Keep having weird dreams.
Who's the medicine for?
Hyo-jin's not feeling well.
She couldn't go to school.
She's burning up.
And where were you while she was so sick?
I was getting her medicine.
What's with you? Take her to the hospital.
What on earth was that?
Turn off the hose first.
Moron...
Just coming into work now, are you?
Hyo-jin wasn't feeling well.
So now you're blaming your daughter?
I'm not making it up.
Did you find your witness?
No, sir.
After turning the whole town upside down.
You think this case is going
to be your big break?
Seong-bok's been calling around.
That's your excuse?
Look at him. He can't even wash the car.
Driving me up the wall.
Even the Chief heard about your witness.
Whether you lied, or let her get away-
you're screwed.
Yes, sir.
This is driving me up the wall.
Don't pay any attention to
the crazy girl's talk.
Not her. I'm talking about this.
Family Tragedy Linked To Wild Mushrooms
"Murdered by... wild mushrooms"?
What did the dermatologist say? Mushrooms?
He wasn't sure,
so he referred Heung-guk to the hospital.
Told you. It can't be the mushrooms.
It's not impossible.
Shut your hole.
You know that story Byeong-gyu told you?
There are so many.
The one about the naked man
eating the deer carcass.
What's gotten into you?
At a crazy time like this?
It's because things are so crazy.
You know the guy who saw it, right?
"Herbs & Tonics"
Over here.
You may not believe it,
but I saw it with my own eyes.
Look at this.
Can you see it?
Sure.
I got 22 stitches.
From falling on your head
while you were drunk?
What are you talking about?
I'm too old to make shit up.
You got proof?
Proof?
Hell yes, proof!
I'm not the kind to talk shit
without backing it up.
Come look at this.
You ready?
Look.
You see?
Empty, right?
I stayed the hell away from
the mountains since that day.
Even put the store up for sale.
How is that proof?
What?
Damn you...
That's not the point.
The point is, when I opened my eyes,
there he was- stark naked
except for a diaper.
A diaper?
That's right.
A grown man?
I'm telling you.
- Grown men can wear diapers.
- Get outta here.
Bladder control problems
are surprisingly common in adults.
But why go into the woods
to treat incontinence?
- Incontinence...
- Am I talking to myself here?
Anyway,
he had his face buried in the carcass,
his body covered in blood...
his eyes all bloodshot.
Then he looked up,
and all of a sudden...
I haven't slept since that day.
- He was chewing on the guts?
- That's right.
- You saw him eating raw flesh?
- Yeah...
Wait, look here.
See where the skin's broken?
Bastard even bit me.
Where does the guy live?
Why, you gonna go there?
I think I should.
Don't. You'll regret it.
It's just a suspicion, but...
You know how the villagers have been
dying out recently?
He's got something to do with it.
He's not human.
Give me his address.
It's out in the middle of nowhere.
You've gotta have a general idea.
It's hard to explain in words.
It's deep in the valley somewhere.
How much further is it?
Still a ways ahead.
Shit!
What's the matter?
It's there.
Over there.
I don't see a house.
Look.
Right over there.
Whoa, isn't that a deer?
So, you weren't making this up.
What did I tell you, dammit?
What in God's name...
What's happening?
Look.
You know...
What's going on?
That should do it, right?
What? You gotta show us the house.
It's just over that hill.
It's just the one house.
You can't miss it.
You came all the way here.
You should see it through.
Don't touch me, I gotta go!
Where do you think you're going?
I said let go!
Shit...
Hey!
Mister.
Mister?
You all right?
You fucking bastards.
We're sorry.
Fuck off.
I'm gonna get your asses sacked.
You just wait.
We're real sorry, okay?
Fuck you.
You deserve to get scorched by lightning.
Where are you going?
You got hit by lightning.
Hey!
What's the point of taking
all those health tonics-
if it's lightning that kills you?
How can something like this happen?
What are the chances?
But they'll say, thanks to all those tonics,
he survived.
Nurse! Nurse!
It's Park Heung-guk in 302!
You gotta come now. It's Park Heung-guk!
It's an emergency!
Doctor!
What's going on?
Can anybody make sense
of what's happening here?
Let's go back to the Jap's house tomorrow.
There's definitely something going on there.
Hyo-jin?
Baby!
Daddy's right here.
Daddy's right here, sweetie.
Look at Daddy.
Hyo-jin!
Look at me.
Look at Daddy.
Daddy's here.
Dad...
- I'm right here.
- Do something, Daddy!
What, sweetie?
Someone keeps banging on the door,
trying to get in.
Who?
A strange man. He's trying to get in.
It's okay, it's okay...
Hyo-jin.
Hyo-jin?
What is this?
You're all right?
Morning, Dad.
But she never eats fish...
Something's wrong with her.
I heard you and Hyo-jin last night.
I asked the old lady next door
to recommend a good shaman.
I'm gonna consult with him,
just so you know.
Got that?
Okay.
Good.
Hey.
Say hello.
This is my nephew.
What, a priest?
Not yet, he's in training. A deacon.
We'll need a translator to talk to the man.
You speak Japanese?
Just a little.
He lived in Japan when he was young.
What's that on your neck?
Nothing.
You've gotta be kidding me.
What's your name, son?
Yang E-sam. (Two-three)
Is that your real name?
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Get in.
Anybody home?
What is it?
Goddamn perv.
Look at this. What does it say?
Uncle, this is illegal.
I know.
Then why... We should stop.
If you won't help, wait outside.
But Uncle!
Okay, you wait outside.
What are you staring at?
Go keep a lookout.
What the fuck?
- Son of a bitch!
- Get over here!
Get him off me!
What were you doing poking
around the doghouse?
Block the door!
Get over here!
Shit!
Seong-bok, you bastard!
Fucking bastard!
Where is it?
Where did it go?
Over there.
Seong-bok.
I think it's the owner.
Seong-bok?
Excuse me.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
What's the matter with you?
Did you get bit?
Say something, dammit.
He's the criminal.
You're scaring me, man.
Snap out of it.
It wasn't just one or two people.
He took pictures of them
when they were alive-
and then went back for more
when they went crazy and died.
What the hell are you going on about?
He's the criminal.
That's enough. I'll deal with you later.
I'm sure of it.
He...
He took his victims' belongings
and did something with them.
What did you see?
Tell me!
Jeon Hyo-jin
You're getting all wet!
Where is Hyo-jin?
In the living room.
Hyo-jin.
You're home early.
Did you lose your trainer?
No, why?
What's this, then?
It's not mine.
Isn't this your handwriting?
I said, it's not mine.
You know anything about
a Japanese man living in the village?
You're dripping water all over the place.
Answer me. Do you know him or not?
Did you meet him?
Answer me.
You're scaring her.
Get out for a sec.
Come on, this is serious. It's you and me.
Daddy is a policeman. I'll know if you lie.
Did you meet this man?
Tell me.
Tell you what?
Everything.
Where you met, what you did.
Why should I tell you?
Because it's important.
What's so important?
Answer me, girl!
I said, what's so important?
What's so damn important?
What the hell...
...is so damned important?
You don't even know what's important.
Stop grilling me, goddamn it!
Fuck!
What are you doing?
I thought you were sleeping.
What the hell?
Yanking up your daughter's skirt
in the middle of the night?
Speak, will you?
Tell me, asshole!
Tell me, you fucking shithead!
Fuck you!
Stop staring, motherfucker!
Don't call your daddy that!
Don't you look at me!
Stop it! Daddy said he was sorry.
I'm gonna kill all of you.
How could you?
I met the shaman today.
He thinks there's a spirit in the house.
Something's possessed Hyo-jin.
And if we don't act,
there'll be dead bodies.
He's supposed to be the best.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Come with me, and don't give me any crap.
Ask him where he stashed
the stuff from in there.
The things in there... where are they now?
What things?
He asks what things.
The stuff we saw before.
Things we saw... before.
The photographs?
You mean the pictures?
Yeah, the pictures. And the other stuff.
Yes.
I burned them.
Sorry?
He burned them.
Where?
In the kitchen.
Bastard!
You!
What did you come here to do?
Ask him again.
To travel.
To travel, he says.
Tell him I'll throw him in jail
if he doesn't fess up.
Tell us the truth.
Even if I told you,
you wouldn't believe me.
He says you wouldn't believe him.
Look, you translate everything I say,
- word for word.
- Yes, sir.
You fucking prick!
Oh...
You loose-assed, dog-fucking son of a whore!
So, uh...
What kind of tourist hangs pictures
of dead people on his wall?
Travel... the dead...
Why was this in your house?
How did this...?
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you?
I know what you're doing in this village.
I saw that room.
And I know what the fuck
you're doing to my daughter!
I want you...
to stop what you're doing,
and leave this village quietly.
I mean it.
Leave.
Quietly.
This is Gokseong. My turf.
Don't mess around
and get yourself killed. Just leave.
If you don't leave, you'll die.
If you heard me, say something.
Or at least nod your fucking head!
Please answer.
So, you're...
Shut up, bitch!
You're blowing me off?
Oh, I'm just not worth answering.
Is that it?
You're not even gonna listen, right?
Ain't that right?
I'm trying to speak to you,
but you're not listening!
What's this?
What the fuck is this?
What the hell is all this?
What the...
What the fuck are these
rituals you're doing?!
What the fuck are you doing in my town!
Do you know whose daughter
you're messing with?
Son of a bitch!
Look out!
Jong-gu?
Now what?
Starting to see the light?
I'll give you three days.
Get out, or you'll end up
like your goddamned dog.
Translate.
Translate what I said.
How long has it been like this?
Just a few days.
So?
The symptoms-
they're the same as the others'.
There's gotta be an explanation
for what she has.
They say they don't know.
What is it?
Oh God!
Who the fuck did this?
What?!
You okay?
Get your husband.
Who did this?
Who the fuck did this?
Jong-gu!
What's the matter!
Does he drink a lot?
It's nothing to worry about.
I'll take the needles out in 20 minutes.
Cut back on the drinking.
Yeah.
It's started. You better brace yourself.
What I said the other day-
we'll do it tomorrow.
Where is Hyo-jin?
You can't back out now.
Get the money for the ritual.
Where is she?
At home. Where else would she be?
I asked the old lady next door to watch her.
You left her alone with a stranger?
Are you out of your minds?
Don't move.
Hyo-jin.
Baby.
- What's the matter?
- Oh my God!
Hyo-jin!
Drop that, baby.
Don't cry. It's okay.
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
Quick! Call 911!
This is all the work of that Jap.
Ever since we went to his house,
my body's been in pain.
I'm burning up. I'm seeing things.
A man's face comes out of the wall.
I don't think he's alive.
We've gotta do something,
or that bastard will get us first.
Shut the damn door!
What's in that jar?
Which one?
The one with the red lid.
It's just soy sauce.
Bring it over.
What, are you deaf?
Out of the way, come on.
Stand back.
What is that?
I'll be fucked...
It's a real wicked spirit we've got here.
You don't want to leave, do you?
Let's go!
Stop it!
Hyo-ijn!
Come here, you!
You met up with something recently
you weren't supposed to?
I don't follow you.
Did you disturb someone?
Of all the evil I've seen,
this is the strongest.
You disturbed it.
Oh, God! What do we do now?
Who is it?
Who did you disturb?
Tell him.
A Japanese man...
I knew it.
That's no man.
That's a ghost.
All the things happening
around here are his doing.
If nothing is done,
it's not just your daughter,
but everything that walks
on two feet will perish.
Sir!
This is Park Chun-bae. He owns this house.
He killed his wife, too?
It appears so.
What's that bastard's name?
Park Chun-bae.
Then what?
What do you mean, what? Gotta get rid of it.
Either banish it, or kill it.
I'm casting a deadly hex tomorrow
at the hour of the dog.
Yes, sir.
You got the money?
How much?
About 10 grand, don't you think?
I'll have it ready.
Good.
Listen.
What I'm doing tomorrow-
it's no ordinary ritual.
I'll be casting a death hex.
It's incredibly dangerous.
So you can't do anything
that would taint it.
No intercourse.
Watch what you eat and drink.
Or the spell will backfire.
Yes, sir.
Okay then. You can go.
Can I ask you something?
What?
That Japanese guy.
You said he's a ghost.
So?
I don't get how a living
person can be a ghost.
It's not a living human.
He died a long time ago.
He must have been human once.
But not anymore.
So then,
the ghost got inside him?
Well, that's how it started.
Not everything that moves,
breathes, and talks is alive.
Countless people have perished
because they didn't understand that.
If it's not stopped...
that demon will destroy this village.
Demon?
An evil ghost!
Even among other demons,
he's a master of evil.
If that's true,
why did it have to be...
...your daughter?
What sin did that young girl ever commit?
Yes.
If you go fishing,
do you know what you'll catch?
No.
He's just fishing.
Not even he knows what he'll catch.
He just threw out the bait,
and your daughter took it.
That's all it was.
Park Chun-bae
- This one?
- No.
Money. Yes, money.
21 dollars more.
- No!
- That's okay.
Oh, come on.
Tell him to stop.
Stop!
I said stop!
Jong-gu!
What's the matter?
Look at me.
Baby?
Hyo-jin!
Please make him stop...
Please...
Please make him stop.
Dad!
Dad...
Hyo-jin.
We shouldn't do this...
Stop, you bastards!
Stop!
Fucking bastards!
Stop right now.
Stop!
Stop.
I said stop!
I'm gonna smash your heads in!
Stop, I said.
Get out.
Now!
Everything started on that day?
I'll try speaking to the Father.
What you're telling me is true?
Yes.
And you said the shaman told you this.
From their perspective,
a ghost is the spirit of a dead man.
But that man is alive.
I've heard about this man, too.
Rumor has it he's a renowned professor.
And there are darker,
more disturbing rumors-
Some say he's a Buddhist monk.
But they're just rumors.
How can you believe them?
No, Father. They're definitely not rumors.
You sound terribly sure.
Did you see it with your own eyes?
How can you be sure
without seeing for yourself?
Take her back to the hospital.
Trust the doctor.
There's nothing the Church
can do for you now.
Come with me to the Jap's.
Sorry?
I gotta see for myself
if he's really a ghost or not.
If he is,
then I won't be able to kill him.
Where is he?
Is everyone here?
Yeah.
Why'd you call us so early?
Cheol-yeong couldn't come.
His sow is farrowing.
What's with your face?
This ain't a joke?
You're serious, right?
Yeah.
Cross your heart, or your mom's a whore?
You prick!
This is no time for jokes.
What a fucking loser.
Go!
- Nothing?
- No.
Don't just stand around. Check the back.
What's that?
Fucking bastard...
Byeong-gyu! Over here.
Hurry up.
Is that him?
Over there.
Where? Follow me.
Where?
What the...?
Who's that?
What is that thing?
Don't come any closer.
Back off.
Stop it.
That's enough, man!
Sorry, man. You all right?
Stop it!
What are you doing to him?
He's not... right...
Put it down.
- Let go!
- We can talk this out.
E- sam!
Dad...
Look.
There's another one!
That's him.
That's him!
Get him!
Where?
Son of a bitch!
There he is.
Over there.
Son of a bitch!
Where is he?
Over there.
Where?
What's wrong?
- Come over here.
- What? Why did you stop?
What's the matter?
Come over here!
Jong-gu.
Where'd he go?
Where is that bastard?
Hey, man!
Get down here.
Do you see him?
Hey!
Where did he go?
Jong-gu!
I gotta catch him.
Gotta catch that bastard.
Catch that bastard.
I can't believe this...
- Gotta save my baby.
- Come on.
Let's go down.
I gotta save my little girl.
- We'll get him.
- I've gotta find him, and save my baby.
- Don't worry, we will.
- Okay?
Get your act together, man.
We gotta save her.
I know, man.
I know.
I have to save my daughter...
Come on, man.
I have to catch that bastard.
Don't cry, man.
Dammit, Jong-gu!
Please, pick up.
Shit! Was that a person?
Wife
The rat fell into the trap.
You all right, baby?
You okay?
I'm okay.
Come here.
You're okay now?
Drink up.
Good girl.
Leave it.
I want to tidy up a little.
Leave it. We've got the shaman
to thank for everything.
Get some rest. You must be exhausted.
Shaman
Damn fool.
Suspect arrested in
the mushroom-tonic case...
Victims have developed
severe mental derangement...
Mr. Yang E-sam?
Yes.
The landlady was a victim.
Your uncle must've taken the tonic, too.
It's turned the town upside down.
We've gotta bring him in.
You should get a lawyer.
After all,
he's a victim, too.
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
Get out.
Missed calls - Shaman
What the hell?
What the...?
Hello.
It's me.
Where are you?
What about you?
Don't ask me anything.
You need to get to your daughter. Now.
Tell me what's going on?
I'm at your place.
Get back to your house, now.
First tell me what's going on.
I...
I misread the divination.
It's not him.
What are you talking about?
I cast the hex on the wrong ghost.
I saw a woman in front of your house.
I made a grave mistake.
A terrible, terrible mistake.
It's not the Japanese man.
That woman is the evil spirit.
It was all her doing.
So, go home now.
I'm on my way there, too.
Then...
Who's the Japanese man?
He was trying to kill that woman
in order to save people from her.
Understand?
That Japanese man-
he's a shaman, like me.
Was the woman...
wearing white?
Did you see her?
A young woman?
That's her.
...defend us in battle.
Be our safeguard against the wickedness
and snares of the devil.
Where is she?
Where's Hyo-jin?!
Hyo-jin!
What is it?
Where are you headed in the dark of night?
I'm asking you.
Where is my daughter?
Where is she?
Girl about this tall?
Yeah.
Hyo-jin?
That's right.
She's possessed by an evil spirit.
The old woman tells me the Jap is a ghost.
He's trying to suck her blood dry...
Shut the fuck up!
Answer me, bitch!
Where is Hyo-jin?
- Have you seen the Jap?
- Where's my daughter?
At your home, where else?
She's not home.
She is.
She just got back.
Don't go now-
or you'll all die.
If you go now,
your whole family will perish.
What are you talking about?
The Jap is waiting for you...
to annihilate your family.
He's dead.
He's not dead.
Death cannot touch him.
The demon will soon enter your home.
You've seen the demon?
At the house of the hanged woman.
It was a dream.
It was no dream.
I laid a trap for it.
Wait here, until he's caught.
That's all you need to do.
What are you?
A woman or a ghost?
Why do you ask?
I need to know...
If I can put my faith in you.
Just believe,
and your family will be saved.
What are you?
Someone trying to save your daughter.
A woman.
I called all her friends...
Hyo-jin?
Hyo-jin!
Baby.
Baby...
When will the demon come?
It's already there.
Hyo-jin.
It's already there?
Let me ask you one thing.
What is your true form?
What do you think is my true form?
The devil.
You're the devil.
Why can't you answer?
You've already said it.
I'm the devil.
Shaman
I'm almost there.
Where are you? Are you home?
I'm with the woman now.
You mustn't let her tempt you.
Never.
Whatever she tells you,
you must go to your daughter now.
Do you understand me?
Understand?
Do you?
Is that your shaman?
Don't believe what he tells you.
They're in on it together.
Isn't that right?
You're already certain I'm the devil.
That's why you came here...
carrying that sickle.
My words, whatever I say-
they won't change your mind.
No.
That's not true.
There's no doubt.
You came here
to confirm your suspicions about me.
That's not true!
If you say
you're not the devil,
and reveal your true form to me-
I'll leave you alone.
When the demon is snared,
the rooster will cry three times.
Wait until the third cry.
You'll leave me alone?
Yes.
Two more.
Do not waver.
You'll leave?
Yes.
I'll leave you alone.
Who said I'd let you leave?
Then let me ask you one thing.
What?
Why in God's name is he doing this?
Because her father has sinned.
What sin?
What sin did I commit?
Her father suspected another.
He tried to kill him, and finally succeeded.
But my daughter...!
My daughter...
My daughter got sick first!
How can that...
How can that possibly...
One more, now.
How can that be...?
Don't do it.
What are you saying?
Whether you walk out of here or not
is completely up to you.
Touch me and see.
A ghost does not have flesh and bones,
and you see I have both.
Park Chun-bae
No.
That's not it.
It's you.
No.
This is all your doing.
Don't do it.
Hyo-jin...
No!
What are you doing?
Don't!
Why are you troubled?
Hyo-jin.
Honey...
Mother...
Look at me.
Look at me!
Please.
Look at me.
Please...
Please!
Hyo-jin!
Hyo-jin...
Hyo-jin.
Hyo-jin!
Why is there doubt in your heart?
See my hands, and my feet.
You can see it is I.
Myself.
Oh Lord...
Hyo-jin...
It's okay.
My baby.
You know Daddy's a policeman.
I'll take care of everything.
Daddy will.